<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:sparkle="http://www.andymatuschak.org/xml-namespaces/sparkle" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>FocusMode Updates</title>
    <item>
      <title>Version 7.1.1</title>
      <sparkle:version>164</sparkle:version>
      <sparkle:shortVersionString>7.1.1</sparkle:shortVersionString>
      <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>13.0</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 14:11:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://github.com/elesinn/focusmo-updates/releases/download/v7.1.1/Focusmo_v7.1.1.dmg" sparkle:edSignature="aNHCekptDx47fuO8rRfdVrJ4AWsF1rRuywz7TFlUaf0dM3rzv5FV1IU0F3YkLfPGvwD6/VCHiKb96j1TdwDgAQ==" length="22218237" type="application/octet-stream"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Version 7.1.0</title>
      <sparkle:version>163</sparkle:version>
      <sparkle:shortVersionString>7.1.0</sparkle:shortVersionString>
      <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>13.0</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
      <description>
&lt;h2&gt;What's New in 7.1.0&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;✨ New Features&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;External Task Manager Integrations&lt;/strong&gt;: Pull tasks from your favorite task managers directly into Focusmo:
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Things 3 Integration&lt;/strong&gt;: Sync your Today tasks from Things 3. Completing a task in Focusmo marks it done in Things 3 automatically.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Apple Reminders Integration&lt;/strong&gt;: Connect your Reminders lists to see tasks in Focusmo. Two-way completion sync keeps both apps in sync.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Integrations Settings&lt;/strong&gt;: New Preferences → Integrations tab to manage all your connected task sources&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source Badges&lt;/strong&gt;: External tasks display their source app icon so you always know where they came from&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project &amp;amp; Area Badges&lt;/strong&gt;: Things 3 tasks show their project and area tags in the task list and Command Palette&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Auto-Refresh&lt;/strong&gt;: External tasks refresh automatically when you activate Focusmo&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Multi-Task Floating Island&lt;/strong&gt;: Focus on multiple tasks at once with the new Big Tasks Island:
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Task Chips&lt;/strong&gt;: See all your active tasks as horizontal chips in the floating timer&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Task Selection Sheet&lt;/strong&gt;: Click to open a searchable sheet to add or remove tasks from your current focus session&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Appearance Toggle&lt;/strong&gt;: Enable Big Tasks Island in Preferences → Appearance&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Periodic Audio Presence Cues&lt;/strong&gt;: Stay grounded during long focus sessions with subtle audio reminders:
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Configurable Intervals&lt;/strong&gt;: Set how often you want to hear a gentle presence cue&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sound Selection&lt;/strong&gt;: Choose from built-in sounds or disable entirely&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Enhanced Things 3 Integration&lt;/strong&gt; (Community Request):
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Time Spent Tags&lt;/strong&gt;: Focusmo automatically adds time-spent tags to Things 3 tasks (e.g., "30m", "1h 15m")&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tag Accumulation&lt;/strong&gt;: Multiple focus sessions on the same task accumulate time in the tag&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;🐛 Bug Fixes&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Fixed AppleScript record parsing for Things 3 project/area metadata&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Fixed permission dialog appearing when Reminders access was already granted&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Fixed connection status not refreshing after sync errors&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
      </description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:36:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://github.com/elesinn/focusmo-updates/releases/download/v7.1.0/Focusmo_v7.1.0.dmg" sparkle:edSignature="BF2nuBooJOpW02UPO2iN+kif8Wg4jTb+CUjKKZCrD0XWxHkAGcOVOWvn7b3FJ3YgIs+lBxAmyybOcDf9WIKFCw==" length="21775353" type="application/octet-stream"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Version 7.0.1</title>
      <sparkle:version>153</sparkle:version>
      <sparkle:shortVersionString>7.0.1</sparkle:shortVersionString>
      <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>13.0</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
      <description>
&lt;h2&gt;What's New in 7.0.1&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;✨ New Features&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Delete Activity Sessions&lt;/strong&gt;: Take full control of your activity log with new delete functionality:
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Delete Focus Sessions&lt;/strong&gt;: Click the trash icon next to "Edit" in session details to remove a focus session and all its tracked activity&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Clear Activity Outside Sessions&lt;/strong&gt;: In the global Activity view, expand "App Usage" and click the trash icon to remove all activity tracked outside of focus sessions&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Delete Individual Activity&lt;/strong&gt;: Right-click any activity entry to delete it from your log&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Customizable Timer Background Color&lt;/strong&gt;: Personalize your focus experience with custom timer background colors. Choose any color that helps you focus, or let it follow your theme automatically.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deep Search in Preferences&lt;/strong&gt;: Find any setting instantly with the new search bar in Preferences — word-by-word fuzzy search across 80+ settings with term highlighting and auto-scroll navigation.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Things 3 Integration&lt;/strong&gt;: QuickAdd now supports Things 3 — capture the currently selected task and start a focus session with one shortcut.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Enhanced Floating Timer&lt;/strong&gt;:
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Countdown Styles&lt;/strong&gt;: Choose between Normal and Minimal display modes&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Custom Minimize Button&lt;/strong&gt;: Title bar minimize button for non-minimal styles&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Position &amp;amp; Size Memory&lt;/strong&gt;: The floating window remembers where you left it&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resize Anywhere&lt;/strong&gt;: Resize the floating timer on any screen, not just the primary display&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wider Timer Support&lt;/strong&gt;: Maximum width increased to 1600px for ultrawide displays&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Task Name Editing in Zen Mode&lt;/strong&gt;: Edit your task name directly from the floating timer's ellipsis menu while in Zen Mode.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hide Break Window&lt;/strong&gt;: New "Hide" button on break windows lets you dismiss the break overlay without skipping the break. Your break timer continues running in the background.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Toggle Session Reflection Notes&lt;/strong&gt;: New setting to hide the reflection prompt after sessions. Find it in General → App Behavior.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;🐛 Bug Fixes&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Fixed dark mode text visibility issues throughout the app by using color-scheme-aware text colors&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Fixed floating timer window losing its width when being recreated&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
      </description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 18:40:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://github.com/elesinn/focusmo-updates/releases/download/v7.0.1/Focusmo_v7.0.1.dmg" sparkle:edSignature="9EOu836aSzDpdJwnSmcBEgt8+CBdvK7bU+VC5DNf4WZwMzhvcfTxPSBcJvGDimQICx5z9jig62AKuA3UtSnsBA==" length="21620471" type="application/octet-stream"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Version 7.0.0</title>
      <sparkle:version>152</sparkle:version>
      <sparkle:shortVersionString>7.0.0</sparkle:shortVersionString>
      <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>13.0</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
      <description>
&lt;h2&gt;What's New in 7.0.0&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;✨ New Features&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Zen Mode&lt;/strong&gt;: A radically minimal focus experience for distraction-free deep work.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Full Pomodoro Cycles&lt;/strong&gt;: Complete work → break → work → long break automation. Set your intervals and let the timer guide you through the entire cycle.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Haptic Feedback System&lt;/strong&gt;: Tactile responses throughout timer interactions for a more physical, grounded experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;🎨 Improvements&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Refined Command Palette&lt;/strong&gt;: Now requires Cmd+Enter to start a task immediately. Enter adds the task to your list.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Smarter Mode Navigation&lt;/strong&gt;: Automatically navigates to Tasks when switching to Zen Mode from Activity or Analytics.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;🐛 Bug Fixes&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Fixed memory leaks from NSEvent monitors, timers, and observers that could cause increased RAM usage during long sessions&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Fixed session completion window appearing in Zen Mode when it should be hidden&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Fixed various edge cases in Zen Mode feature visibility&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
      </description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 10:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://github.com/elesinn/focusmo-updates/releases/download/v7.0.0/Focusmo_v7.0.0.dmg" sparkle:edSignature="o3SWGuy6rS3CvNgMEqyNZG0hEHkUFoFZOj6PkIiz7ys5WTTQTWtSwRqP2V0jkFp4jszlWJro3IJtkH0nEPEQBQ==" length="21680687" type="application/octet-stream"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Version 6.2.0</title>
      <sparkle:version>52</sparkle:version>
      <sparkle:shortVersionString>6.2.0</sparkle:shortVersionString>
      <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>13.0</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
      <description>
&lt;h2&gt;What's New in 6.2.0&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;✨ New Features&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gamification System&lt;/strong&gt;: Stay motivated with a new gamification layer:
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Badges&lt;/strong&gt;: Earn badges for focus milestones — first session, focus marathon, early bird, night owl, and more. Track your progress toward unlocking new achievements.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Streak Tracking&lt;/strong&gt;: Build a daily focus streak and watch it grow. Streak freeze shields protect your streak when life gets in the way.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Celebrations&lt;/strong&gt;: Unlock badges with satisfying particle effects and celebratory overlays. Every milestone feels like an achievement.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Workspace Task Filtering&lt;/strong&gt;: Filter your task list by workspace with a sleek new filter bar. Quickly focus on tasks from a specific workspace, or view everything at once.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Redesigned Daily Goal Screen&lt;/strong&gt;: Your new gamification hub — see your streak, browse all badges, and track daily progress with a scrollable 30-day chart. Three tabs: Today, Records, and History.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Improved Focus Lock Navigation&lt;/strong&gt;: Navigate back to Tasks during active focus sessions without stopping your timer. Press the play button to return to the timer view.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;🎨 Improvements&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Streamlined Navigation&lt;/strong&gt;: The app now opens directly to Tasks as your home screen. Activity is now a dedicated section — cleaner, faster, less clutter.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Collapsible Activity Sections&lt;/strong&gt;: Insights in the Activity screen now collapse and expand with smooth animations.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Polished Animations&lt;/strong&gt;: Animated numbers that count up, spring animations on progress rings and bar charts, subtle hover effects on cards.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Keyboard Navigation for Analytics&lt;/strong&gt;: Use arrow keys to navigate between metric cards. Press Enter to drill down into details.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cleaner Dashboard&lt;/strong&gt;: Teasers now tap to navigate instead of opening dead-end popovers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;🐛 Bug Fixes&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Fixed Command Palette losing focus in certain conditions&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Fixed DND shortcuts opening the Shortcuts app instead of running silently&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Fixed keyboard shortcuts not working in session completion modal&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
      </description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 17:34:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://github.com/elesinn/focusmo-updates/releases/download/v6.2.0/Focusmo_v6.2.0.dmg" sparkle:edSignature="OvzU+yFQFLQv9lNMGdmqi5VRoPxINJ1H6zaXOARwpXt+VhWfSqH5wIA+1MuhZ48Ypk3hT9UsWEpArJWTLapADA==" length="20915385" type="application/octet-stream"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Version 6.1.4</title>
      <sparkle:version>42</sparkle:version>
      <sparkle:shortVersionString>6.1.4</sparkle:shortVersionString>
      <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>13.0</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
      <description>
&lt;h2&gt;What's New in 6.1.4&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;✨ New Features&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Command Palette&lt;/strong&gt;: Press your preferred keyboard shortcut to instantly search tasks, start focus sessions, or create new tasks — all from one place. Type natural durations like "30m", "1.5h", or "until 5pm" to set your focus time. Drag the palette anywhere on screen and it remembers where you left it.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Focus Mode Integration (Pro)&lt;/strong&gt;: Focusmo now automatically enables Do Not Disturb when you start a focus session. No more distractions from notifications. Toggle DND right from the floating timer bar.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Keyboard-First Task Management&lt;/strong&gt;: Navigate your task list without touching the mouse — J/K to move up and down, Enter to expand task details, C to create a new task, E to edit the selected task.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expandable Task Details&lt;/strong&gt;: Double-click any task to see the full picture — time estimates, elapsed time, and when it was last modified.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interactive Widgets&lt;/strong&gt;: Complete tasks directly from your desktop widgets with a single tap.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;🎨 Improvements&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Redesigned Bulk App Manager&lt;/strong&gt;: The app blocking matrix now has freeze panes — the app name column and header row stay visible as you scroll through large lists. The window is also resizable for better visibility.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Smoother Drag &amp;amp; Drop&lt;/strong&gt;: Reordering tasks now feels premium with lift effects, subtle rotation, and smooth animations as tasks make room for each other.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Better Visual Feedback&lt;/strong&gt;: Tasks now lift slightly on hover and show a clear focus ring when navigating with the keyboard.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;🐛 Bug Fixes&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Fixed drag &amp;amp; drop not working in some cases&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Fixed tasks sometimes moving to the wrong position when reordering&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Fixed tasks getting visually stuck after dragging&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Fixed Daily Goal section missing from navigation&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Fixed session pause/resume state getting out of sync&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
      </description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 12:08:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://github.com/elesinn/focusmo-updates/releases/download/v6.1.4/Focusmo_v6.1.4.dmg" sparkle:edSignature="pH0BTCsbdGthwik/WTewpyI9+lX5XbZIpwXMTToeY5EQ5WZ4S3RUYwXweuaaJQra7qoZoU7OcDzCFfUlwAG6BA==" length="21221895" type="application/octet-stream"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Version 6.1.3</title>
      <sparkle:version>41</sparkle:version>
      <sparkle:shortVersionString>6.1.3</sparkle:shortVersionString>
      <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>13.0</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
      <description>
&lt;h2&gt;What's New in 6.1.3&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;✨ New Features&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Task vs Session Clarity&lt;/strong&gt;: New "Mark task as complete" toggle on the session completion screen. Now you can choose whether finishing a session also completes the task — addressing confusion between session completion and task completion.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;🎨 Improvements&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Remaining Time Display&lt;/strong&gt;: Task list now shows "X left" suffix for tasks with remaining estimated time.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Celebration Window Focus&lt;/strong&gt;: Session completion celebration now properly activates and comes to front.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;🔄 Changes&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cross-Device Sync&lt;/strong&gt;: Temporarily disabled while mobile app development is in progress. Shows "Coming Soon" badge in Preferences.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
      </description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 10:37:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://github.com/elesinn/focusmo-updates/releases/download/v6.1.3/Focusmo_v6.1.3.dmg" sparkle:edSignature="1/JfpJkl/ZAjgZdx5alMks8tS29vR5GzMPcQEaziyLscCnl7+qrCgi3iUCSsx6/Qm9WJ9dGbg3gCyf+50p+ACA==" length="20222623" type="application/octet-stream"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Version 6.1.2</title>
      <sparkle:version>40</sparkle:version>
      <sparkle:shortVersionString>6.1.2</sparkle:shortVersionString>
      <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>13.0</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
      <description>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;**Google Sign-In**: Sign in with your Google account to sync your data across devices and keep your progress backed up to the cloud. Your account info appears in Preferences.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;**Redesigned Onboarding**: Completely new first-time experience guides you through setting daily focus goals, introduces the task manager, walks through setup steps, and helps you start your first focus session.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;**Theme Selection**: New theme options in Preferences → Appearance:&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;**Browser Activity Tracking**: Focusmo now tracks which websites you're visiting during focus sessions. Supports 15 browsers:&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;**Click-Through Mode for Floating Timer**: Enable in Preferences → Appearance to make the floating timer transparent and click-through — it stays visible but won't interfere with your work. Perfect for gaming or presentations.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;**Quick Navigation to Activity**: Right-click any task and select "View in Activity" to instantly jump to that task's session history. The Activity screen scrolls to the right section and expands the task automatically.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;**One-Click Accessibility Setup**: When Focusmo needs accessibility permissions, click the notification badge to open System Settings directly to the right page.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;**Freemium Model Updates**: &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;**Activity Screen**: The "All Sessions" list is now available for weekly, monthly, and yearly views — not just daily. See your complete session history regardless of time range.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;**Faster Task Statistics**: Task time details now preload when you view tasks, so stats appear instantly without loading spinners.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;**Smoother Animations**: &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;**Unified Design System**: Consistent colors, spacing, and typography throughout the app. All colors now respect your selected theme.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;**Bundle ID Migration**: If you're upgrading from an older version, your settings, preferences, and iCloud data are automatically migrated to the new app identifier.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed memory leaks in 9 timer-related components that could cause increased RAM usage over time&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed animation glitches caused by dynamic view identifiers&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed threading violations that could cause occasional UI freezes&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed crash safety by replacing fatalError calls with graceful error handling&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed menu bar widget showing incorrect version number&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed pulse animations stacking up and becoming too intense&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed iCloud sync issues for users with accessibility-restricted environments&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 12:08:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://github.com/elesinn/focusmo-updates/releases/download/v6.1.2/Focusmo_v6.1.2.dmg" sparkle:edSignature="FP7hYCDSX5UxVDx6xBM7TAueP3FSiiSEF/V2O6ddJYcfm4uA46cQsxFScD1JI3B6FlfeImsh7MzUJB27j1ZpAw==" length="19359065" type="application/octet-stream"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Version 6.1.2</title>
      <sparkle:version>39</sparkle:version>
      <sparkle:shortVersionString>6.1.2</sparkle:shortVersionString>
      <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>13.0</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
      <description>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;**Google Sign-In**: Sign in with your Google account to sync your data across devices and keep your progress backed up to the cloud. Your account info appears in Preferences.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;**Redesigned Onboarding**: Completely new first-time experience guides you through setting daily focus goals, introduces the task manager, walks through setup steps, and helps you start your first focus session.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;**Theme Selection**: New theme options in Preferences → Appearance:&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;**Browser Activity Tracking**: Focusmo now tracks which websites you're visiting during focus sessions. Supports 15 browsers:&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;**Click-Through Mode for Floating Timer**: Enable in Preferences → Appearance to make the floating timer transparent and click-through — it stays visible but won't interfere with your work. Perfect for gaming or presentations.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;**Quick Navigation to Activity**: Right-click any task and select "View in Activity" to instantly jump to that task's session history. The Activity screen scrolls to the right section and expands the task automatically.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;**One-Click Accessibility Setup**: When Focusmo needs accessibility permissions, click the notification badge to open System Settings directly to the right page.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;**Freemium Model Updates**: &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;**Activity Screen**: The "All Sessions" list is now available for weekly, monthly, and yearly views — not just daily. See your complete session history regardless of time range.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;**Faster Task Statistics**: Task time details now preload when you view tasks, so stats appear instantly without loading spinners.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;**Smoother Animations**: &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;**Unified Design System**: Consistent colors, spacing, and typography throughout the app. All colors now respect your selected theme.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;**Bundle ID Migration**: If you're upgrading from an older version, your settings, preferences, and iCloud data are automatically migrated to the new app identifier.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed memory leaks in 9 timer-related components that could cause increased RAM usage over time&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed animation glitches caused by dynamic view identifiers&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed threading violations that could cause occasional UI freezes&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed crash safety by replacing fatalError calls with graceful error handling&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed menu bar widget showing incorrect version number&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed pulse animations stacking up and becoming too intense&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed iCloud sync issues for users with accessibility-restricted environments&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 12:07:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://github.com/elesinn/focusmo-updates/releases/download/v6.1.2/Focusmo_v6.1.2.dmg" sparkle:edSignature="FP7hYCDSX5UxVDx6xBM7TAueP3FSiiSEF/V2O6ddJYcfm4uA46cQsxFScD1JI3B6FlfeImsh7MzUJB27j1ZpAw==" length="19359065" type="application/octet-stream"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Version 6.1.2</title>
      <sparkle:version>39</sparkle:version>
      <sparkle:shortVersionString>6.1.2</sparkle:shortVersionString>
      <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>13.0</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
      <description>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;**Google Sign-In**: Sign in with your Google account to sync your data across devices and keep your progress backed up to the cloud. Your account info appears in Preferences.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;**Redesigned Onboarding**: Completely new first-time experience guides you through setting daily focus goals, introduces the task manager, walks through setup steps, and helps you start your first focus session.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;**Theme Selection**: New theme options in Preferences → Appearance:&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;**Browser Activity Tracking**: Focusmo now tracks which websites you're visiting during focus sessions. Supports 15 browsers:&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;**Click-Through Mode for Floating Timer**: Enable in Preferences → Appearance to make the floating timer transparent and click-through — it stays visible but won't interfere with your work. Perfect for gaming or presentations.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;**Quick Navigation to Activity**: Right-click any task and select "View in Activity" to instantly jump to that task's session history. The Activity screen scrolls to the right section and expands the task automatically.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;**One-Click Accessibility Setup**: When Focusmo needs accessibility permissions, click the notification badge to open System Settings directly to the right page.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;**Freemium Model Updates**: &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;**Activity Screen**: The "All Sessions" list is now available for weekly, monthly, and yearly views — not just daily. See your complete session history regardless of time range.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;**Faster Task Statistics**: Task time details now preload when you view tasks, so stats appear instantly without loading spinners.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;**Smoother Animations**: &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;**Unified Design System**: Consistent colors, spacing, and typography throughout the app. All colors now respect your selected theme.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;**Bundle ID Migration**: If you're upgrading from an older version, your settings, preferences, and iCloud data are automatically migrated to the new app identifier.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed memory leaks in 9 timer-related components that could cause increased RAM usage over time&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed animation glitches caused by dynamic view identifiers&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed threading violations that could cause occasional UI freezes&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed crash safety by replacing fatalError calls with graceful error handling&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed menu bar widget showing incorrect version number&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed pulse animations stacking up and becoming too intense&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed iCloud sync issues for users with accessibility-restricted environments&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 12:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://github.com/elesinn/focusmo-updates/releases/download/v6.1.2/Focusmo_v6.1.2.dmg" sparkle:edSignature="EBKYCw3kfg6J5oLQ6ug40GffwpoHv2Cuii6t6KXXWptbjSxxNn5h2LjWE6ELq/dQUby6/vs61/ndfWd5vvkYBA==" length="19117690" type="application/octet-stream"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Version 6.1.1</title>
      <sparkle:version>39</sparkle:version>
      <sparkle:shortVersionString>6.1.1</sparkle:shortVersionString>
      <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>13.0</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
      <description>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;**Google Sign-In**: Sign in with your Google account to sync your data across devices and keep your progress backed up to the cloud. Your account info appears in Preferences.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;**Redesigned Onboarding**: Completely new first-time experience guides you through setting daily focus goals, introduces the task manager, walks through setup steps, and helps you start your first focus session.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;**Theme Selection**: New theme options in Preferences → Appearance:&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;**Browser Activity Tracking**: Focusmo now tracks which websites you're visiting during focus sessions. Supports 15 browsers:&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;**Click-Through Mode for Floating Timer**: Enable in Preferences → Appearance to make the floating timer transparent and click-through — it stays visible but won't interfere with your work. Perfect for gaming or presentations.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;**Quick Navigation to Activity**: Right-click any task and select "View in Activity" to instantly jump to that task's session history. The Activity screen scrolls to the right section and expands the task automatically.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;**One-Click Accessibility Setup**: When Focusmo needs accessibility permissions, click the notification badge to open System Settings directly to the right page.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;**Freemium Model Updates**: &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;**Activity Screen**: The "All Sessions" list is now available for weekly, monthly, and yearly views — not just daily. See your complete session history regardless of time range.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;**Faster Task Statistics**: Task time details now preload when you view tasks, so stats appear instantly without loading spinners.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;**Smoother Animations**: &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;**Unified Design System**: Consistent colors, spacing, and typography throughout the app. All colors now respect your selected theme.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;**Bundle ID Migration**: If you're upgrading from an older version, your settings, preferences, and iCloud data are automatically migrated to the new app identifier.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed memory leaks in 9 timer-related components that could cause increased RAM usage over time&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed animation glitches caused by dynamic view identifiers&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed threading violations that could cause occasional UI freezes&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed crash safety by replacing fatalError calls with graceful error handling&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed menu bar widget showing incorrect version number&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed pulse animations stacking up and becoming too intense&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed iCloud sync issues for users with accessibility-restricted environments&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 12:12:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://github.com/elesinn/focusmo-updates/releases/download/v6.1.1/Focusmo_v6.1.1.dmg" sparkle:edSignature="8j4x8CCmo+UmquBv+VqpvrOcaJBfV7iGEgU+cjYr+n2R4lWUe9c9uJoheo5NsM1wOf5hjHSO5LBlPVpIj/9BAw==" length="13491168" type="application/octet-stream"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Version 6.1.1</title>
      <sparkle:version>39</sparkle:version>
      <sparkle:shortVersionString>6.1.1</sparkle:shortVersionString>
      <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>13.0</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
      <description>
&lt;h2&gt;What's New in 6.1.1&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;✨ New Features&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Google Sign-In&lt;/strong&gt;: Sign in with your Google account to sync your data across devices&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Redesigned Onboarding&lt;/strong&gt;: New guided setup for goals, task manager intro, and first focus session&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Theme Selection&lt;/strong&gt;: Choose Light/Dark/System appearance and Classic or Pastel color palettes&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Browser Activity Tracking&lt;/strong&gt;: Track websites during focus sessions across 15 browsers (Safari, Chrome, Firefox, Edge, Brave, Opera, Arc, Vivaldi, and more)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Click-Through Mode&lt;/strong&gt;: Make floating timer transparent and non-interactive for gaming or presentations&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;View in Activity&lt;/strong&gt;: Right-click any task to jump directly to its session history&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;One-Click Accessibility Setup&lt;/strong&gt;: Click permission badge to open System Settings directly&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;🎨 Improvements&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Freemium Updates&lt;/strong&gt;: Free users get all analytics views (3-day history) and Pomodoro presets&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Activity Screen&lt;/strong&gt;: All Sessions list now available for all time ranges&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Faster Stats&lt;/strong&gt;: Task statistics preload instantly&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Smoother Animations&lt;/strong&gt;: Improved wave animation and session list transitions&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Unified Design&lt;/strong&gt;: Consistent colors and typography throughout&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;🐛 Bug Fixes&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Fixed memory leaks in timer components&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Fixed animation glitches and UI freezes&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Improved crash safety and error handling&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Fixed menu bar widget version display&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
      </description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 11:35:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://github.com/elesinn/focusmo-updates/releases/download/v6.1.1/Focusmo_v6.1.1.dmg" sparkle:edSignature="8j4x8CCmo+UmquBv+VqpvrOcaJBfV7iGEgU+cjYr+n2R4lWUe9c9uJoheo5NsM1wOf5hjHSO5LBlPVpIj/9BAw==" length="13491168" type="application/octet-stream"/>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
